<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rvData xmlns="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/spreadsheetml/2017/richdata" count="90"><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=anao5r&amp;q=XTAI%3a1513&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>CHUNG-HSIN ELECTRIC &amp; MACHINERY MFG. CORP. (XTAI:1513)</v><v>2</v><v>3</v><v>Finance</v><v>4</v><v>en-US</v><v>anao5r</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>189</v><v>104</v><v>1.0105999999999999</v><v>-6</v><v>-4.0267999999999998E-2</v><v>TWD</v><v>Chung-Hsin Electric &amp; Machinery Mfg Corp is a Taiwan-based company mainly engaged in the motor and energy business. The Company provides design and manufacturing of booster/substations, geographic information system (GIS) operators, and medium-voltage switchgear; comprehensive new energy solutions; parking lot planning and management; air conditioning and refrigeration products, generators, and electronic meters; contracting and construction of power transmission and distribution systems and power monitoring systems, and electrical pipeline installation; contracting and construction of wind, hydro, and solar power generation, energy storage, and turnkey substation and booster station projects, incinerators and pollution control projects; residential and building development, leasing, and sales; and manufacturing of precision-machined components, aerospace components, panels, and semiconductor device cavities. The products are primarily sold domestically.</v><v>3301</v><v>Taiwan Stock Exchange</v><v>XTAI</v><v>XTAI</v><v>3F, No.801, Chung Cheng Road, Zhonghe District, NEW TAIPEI, NEW TAIPEI, 235 TW</v><v>149.5</v><v>Machinery, Equipment &amp; Components</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.39644675926</v><v>0</v><v>142.5</v><v>71945087500</v><v>CHUNG-HSIN ELECTRIC &amp; MACHINERY MFG. CORP.</v><v>CHUNG-HSIN ELECTRIC &amp; MACHINERY MFG. CORP.</v><v>148</v><v>18.5473</v><v>149</v><v>143</v><v>503112500</v><v>1513</v><v>CHUNG-HSIN ELECTRIC &amp; MACHINERY MFG. CORP. (XTAI:1513)</v><v>8045101</v><v>3190540</v><v>1962</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>1</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=anbju2&amp;q=XTAI%3a2882A&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="3"><v>5</v><v>CATHAY FINANCIAL HOLDING CO., LTD. (XTAI:2882A)</v><v>2</v><v>6</v><v>Finance</v><v>4</v><v>en-US</v><v>anbju2</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>62.4</v><v>60.2</v><v>0.69520000000000004</v><v>0.1</v><v>1.6130000000000001E-3</v><v>TWD</v><v>Cathay Financial Holding Co Ltd is a Taiwan-based financial holding company principally engaged in the investment and the management of investment business. The Company operates through five business segments. Banking Operating segment engages in commercial bank businesses, including foreign exchange business, guarantee business, and others. Life Insurance Operating segment engages in interest-sensitive sales of traditional insurance, investment-linked insurance and providing financial planning services. Property Insurance Operating segment engages in fire insurance, marine insurance, land and air insurance, liability insurance, and other insurance. Securities Operating segment engages in brokerage, dealership, and underwriting business. Other Operating segment includes assets, liabilities, revenue and expenditures which cannot be directly attributable to or reasonably allocated to certain operating segments.</v><v>51797</v><v>Taiwan Stock Exchange</v><v>XTAI</v><v>XTAI</v><v>No.296, Section 4, Renai Road, Da'n District, TAIPEI, TAIPEI, 106 TW</v><v>62.1</v><v>Insurance</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.396539351852</v><v>3</v><v>61.9</v><v>1006175871000</v><v>CATHAY FINANCIAL HOLDING CO., LTD.</v><v>CATHAY FINANCIAL HOLDING CO., LTD.</v><v>61.9</v><v>62</v><v>62.1</v><v>16202510000</v><v>2882A</v><v>CATHAY FINANCIAL HOLDING CO., LTD. (XTAI:2882A)</v><v>100420</v><v>22904730</v><v>2001</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>4</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1mou2&amp;q=XNAS%3aAAPL&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>APPLE INC. (XNAS:AAPL)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1mou2</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>288.62</v><v>169.21010000000001</v><v>1.1039000000000001</v><v>1.83</v><v>7.4199999999999995E-3</v><v>USD</v><v>Apple Inc. designs, manufactures and markets smartphones, personal computers, tablets, wearables and accessories, and sells a variety of related services. Its product categories include iPhone, Mac, iPad, and Wearables, Home and Accessories. Its software platforms include iOS, iPadOS, macOS, watchOS, visionOS, and tvOS. Its services include advertising, AppleCare, cloud services, digital content and payment services. The Company operates various platforms, including the App Store, that allow customers to discover and download applications and digital content, such as books, music, video, games and podcasts. It also offers digital content through subscription-based services, including Apple Arcade, Apple Fitness+, Apple Music, Apple News+, and Apple TV+. Its products include iPhone 16 Pro, iPhone 16, iPhone 15, iPhone 14, iPhone SE, MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, iMac, Mac mini, Mac Studio, Mac Pro, iPad Pro, iPad Air, AirPods, AirPods Pro, AirPods Max, Apple TV, Apple Vision Pro and others.</v><v>166000</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>One Apple Park Way, CUPERTINO, CA, 95014 US</v><v>249.27</v><v>Computers, Phones &amp; Household Electronics</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587187777346</v><v>6</v><v>247.64</v><v>3653032842000</v><v>APPLE INC.</v><v>APPLE INC.</v><v>247.9</v><v>31.566099999999999</v><v>246.63</v><v>248.46</v><v>14702700000</v><v>AAPL</v><v>APPLE INC. (XNAS:AAPL)</v><v>4536984</v><v>41435130</v><v>1977</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>7</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=anb1k2&amp;q=XTAI%3a2308&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>DELTA ELECTRONICS, INC. (XTAI:2308)</v><v>2</v><v>3</v><v>Finance</v><v>4</v><v>en-US</v><v>anb1k2</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>1565</v><v>275</v><v>1.3144</v><v>-105</v><v>-7.0707000000000006E-2</v><v>TWD</v><v>Delta Electronics Inc is a Taiwan-based company principally engaged in the manufacture and sales of power supplies and components. The Company operates through three segments. Power Supply and Components segment provides components, embedded power supplies, automotive electronics, commercial products, mobile power supplies, fans and thermal management solutions. The Automation segment provides industrial automation, building automation and other services. The Infrastructure segment provides information infrastructure, energy infrastructure and industrial solutions, and projection business. The Company's products are mainly sold to the United States, Europe, Japan and other regions.</v><v>68000</v><v>Taiwan Stock Exchange</v><v>XTAI</v><v>XTAI</v><v>No. 186, Ruey Kuang Road, Neihu District, TAIPEI, TAIPEI, 114 TW</v><v>1470</v><v>Machinery, Equipment &amp; Components</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.396481481483</v><v>9</v><v>1365</v><v>3584609340000</v><v>DELTA ELECTRONICS, INC.</v><v>DELTA ELECTRONICS, INC.</v><v>1465</v><v>59.637</v><v>1485</v><v>1380</v><v>2597543000</v><v>2308</v><v>DELTA ELECTRONICS, INC. (XTAI:2308)</v><v>21389778</v><v>12352850</v><v>1975</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>10</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=anbkc7&amp;q=XTAI%3a2887E&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="3"><v>5</v><v>TS Financial Holding Co., Ltd. (XTAI:2887E)</v><v>2</v><v>6</v><v>Finance</v><v>4</v><v>en-US</v><v>anbkc7</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>51.7</v><v>48</v><v>0.64490000000000003</v><v>0</v><v>0</v><v>TWD</v><v>TS Financial Holding Co Ltd, formerly Taishin Financial Holding Co Ltd, is a Taiwan-based financial holding company that mainly engages in investment and management of invested businesses. It mainly engages in various financial businesses. Banking subsidiaries engage in wealth management, consumer finance, digital finance, corporate finance and others. Insurance subsidiaries engage in personal insurance business, and the underwriting items include life insurance, medical insurance and others. Securities and investment trust subsidiaries engage in securities brokerage, proprietary and underwriting, public funds and others. Its subsidiaries also engage in balancing new investment and risk control business, financial institution monetary debt purchase, financial institution monetary debt evaluation or auction, financial institution monetary debt management and overdue accounts receivable management services, and securities investment consulting.</v><v>8937</v><v>Taiwan Stock Exchange</v><v>XTAI</v><v>XTAI</v><v>12F/13F/15F/16F/21F/22F/23F, No. 118, Section 4, Renai Road, Daan District, TAIPEI, TAIPEI, 106 TW</v><v>50.6</v><v>Banking Services</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.396539351852</v><v>12</v><v>50.4</v><v>607890600000</v><v>TS Financial Holding Co., Ltd.</v><v>TS Financial Holding Co., Ltd.</v><v>50.4</v><v>50.5</v><v>50.5</v><v>29357490000</v><v>2887E</v><v>TS Financial Holding Co., Ltd. (XTAI:2887E)</v><v>121571</v><v>72682410</v><v>2002</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>13</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a2rb7w&amp;q=OTCM%3aABML&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>AMERICAN BATTERY TECHNOLOGY COMPANY (XNAS:ABAT)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a2rb7w</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>11.49</v><v>0.86019999999999996</v><v>1.0944</v><v>0.12</v><v>4.7808999999999997E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>American Battery Technology Company is an integrated battery materials company. The Company is engaged in the exploration of new primary resources of battery metals, the development and commercialization of new technologies for the extraction and refining of these battery metals from primary resources, and the commercialization of an internally developed integrated process for the recycling of lithium-ion batteries. The Company’s business includes lithium-ion battery recycling and Primary Resource Development &amp; Refining. The Company’s recycling system is a two-phase process: an automated de-manufacturing process followed by a targeted chemical extraction train to separate the individual high-value metals. The Company has designed and optimizing internally developed sustainable lithium extraction process for the manufacturing of battery cathode grade lithium hydroxide from Nevada-based sedimentary claystone primary resources.</v><v>157</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>100 WASHINGTON STREET, SUITE 100, RENO, NV, 89503 US</v><v>2.65</v><v>Metals &amp; Mining</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587052812501</v><v>15</v><v>2.54</v><v>346395196</v><v>AMERICAN BATTERY TECHNOLOGY COMPANY</v><v>AMERICAN BATTERY TECHNOLOGY COMPANY</v><v>2.54</v><v>0</v><v>2.5099999999999998</v><v>2.63</v><v>131709200</v><v>ABAT</v><v>AMERICAN BATTERY TECHNOLOGY COMPANY (XNAS:ABAT)</v><v>633604</v><v>3407336</v><v>2011</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>16</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=anb2p2&amp;q=XTAI%3a2330&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (XTAI:2330)</v><v>2</v><v>3</v><v>Finance</v><v>4</v><v>en-US</v><v>anb2p2</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>2025</v><v>780</v><v>1.4259999999999999</v><v>-20</v><v>-1.1235999999999999E-2</v><v>TWD</v><v>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co Ltd is a Taiwan-based integrated circuit foundry service provider. The Company is primarily engaged in integrated circuit manufacturing services. It offers advanced process technologies, specialised process solutions, advanced photomask and silicon stacking, and packaging-related technologies, while supporting a comprehensive design ecosystem. The Company's products serve diverse electronic sectors including artificial intelligence, high-performance computing, wired and wireless communications, automotive and industrial equipment, personal computing, information applications, consumer electronics, smart internet of things, and wearable devices.</v><v>52045</v><v>Taiwan Stock Exchange</v><v>XTAI</v><v>XTAI</v><v>No.8, Li-Hsin 6th Road, Hsinchu Science Park, HSINCHU, HSINCHU, 300 TW</v><v>1790</v><v>Semiconductors &amp; Semiconductor Equipment</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.396481481483</v><v>18</v><v>1760</v><v>45641252800000</v><v>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited</v><v>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited</v><v>1775</v><v>26.565999999999999</v><v>1780</v><v>1760</v><v>25932530000</v><v>2330</v><v>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (XTAI:2330)</v><v>75832456</v><v>35800960</v><v>1987</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>19</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1ndww&amp;q=XNAS%3aAMD&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>ADVANCED MICRO DEVICES, INC. (XNAS:AMD)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1ndww</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>267.07990000000001</v><v>76.48</v><v>1.9277</v><v>4.3201000000000001</v><v>2.2037000000000001E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. is a global semiconductor company. The Company is focused on high-performance computing and artificial intelligence (AI). Its segments include Data Center, Client and Gaming, and Embedded. Data Center segment includes AI accelerators, microprocessors (CPUs) for servers, graphics processing units (GPUs), accelerated processing units (APUs), data processing units (DPUs), Field Programmable Gate Arrays (FPGAs), and Adaptive system-on-Chip (SoC) products for data centers. Client and Gaming segment includes CPUs, APUs, chipsets for desktops and notebooks, discrete GPUs, and semi-custom SoC products and development services. Embedded segment includes embedded CPUs, APUs, FPGAs, system on modules (SOMs), and Adaptive SoC products. It markets and sells its products under the AMD trademark. Its products include AMD EPYC, AMD Ryzen, AMD Ryzen PRO, Virtex UltraScale+, among others.</v><v>31000</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>2485 Augustine Drive, SANTA CLARA, CA, 95054 US</v><v>201.3</v><v>Semiconductors &amp; Semiconductor Equipment</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587161353906</v><v>21</v><v>196.88</v><v>326654885073</v><v>ADVANCED MICRO DEVICES, INC.</v><v>ADVANCED MICRO DEVICES, INC.</v><v>198.16</v><v>76.931399999999996</v><v>196.04</v><v>200.36009999999999</v><v>1630339000</v><v>AMD</v><v>ADVANCED MICRO DEVICES, INC. (XNAS:AMD)</v><v>4993327</v><v>36032579</v><v>1969</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>22</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=anbkkr&amp;q=XTAI%3a2890&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>SINOPAC FINANCIAL HOLDINGS COMPANY LIMITED (XTAI:2890)</v><v>2</v><v>3</v><v>Finance</v><v>4</v><v>en-US</v><v>anbkkr</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>33.450000000000003</v><v>18.38</v><v>0.58430000000000004</v><v>-0.05</v><v>-1.6259999999999998E-3</v><v>TWD</v><v>Sinopac Financial Holdings Co Ltd is a Taiwan-based financial holding company primarily engaged in financial business. Its investments include banking, bill financing, credit card services, trust services, insurance, securities, futures, venture capital, investments in foreign financial institutions approved by the competent authorities, other businesses deemed by the competent authorities to be related to financial business, and other legally permitted non-financial related businesses. The Company's main business operations include banking, securities, and others. Its service area is primarily in the Greater China region of the Pacific, including Taiwan, the United States, mainland China, Hong Kong, Macau and Vietnam.</v><v>15448</v><v>Taiwan Stock Exchange</v><v>XTAI</v><v>XTAI</v><v>3F, 5F-13F, No. 306, Section 2, Bade Road, Jhongshan District, TAIPEI, TAIPEI, 104 TW</v><v>31</v><v>Banking Services</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.396539351852</v><v>24</v><v>30.5</v><v>444914224000</v><v>SINOPAC FINANCIAL HOLDINGS COMPANY LIMITED</v><v>SINOPAC FINANCIAL HOLDINGS COMPANY LIMITED</v><v>30.55</v><v>16.5946</v><v>30.75</v><v>30.7</v><v>14492320000</v><v>2890</v><v>SINOPAC FINANCIAL HOLDINGS COMPANY LIMITED (XTAI:2890)</v><v>27525581</v><v>25489500</v><v>2002</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>25</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1nhlh&amp;q=XNAS%3aAMZN&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>AMAZON.COM, INC. (XNAS:AMZN)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1nhlh</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>258.60000000000002</v><v>161.38</v><v>1.3667</v><v>5.31</v><v>2.6424E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Amazon.com, Inc. provides a range of products and services to customers. The products offered through its stores include merchandise and content it has purchased for resale and products offered by third-party sellers. The Company’s segments include North America, International and Amazon Web Services (AWS). It serves consumers through its online and physical stores and focuses on selection, price, and convenience. Customers access its offerings through its websites, mobile apps, Alexa, devices, streaming, and physically visiting its stores. It also manufactures and sells electronic devices, including Kindle, Fire tablet, Fire TV, Echo, Ring, Blink, and eero, and develops and produces media content. It serves developers and enterprises of all sizes, including start-ups, government agencies, and academic institutions, through AWS, which offers a set of on-demand technology services, including compute, storage, database, analytics, and machine learning, and other services.</v><v>1576000</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>410 Terry Avenue North, SEATTLE, WA, 98109 US</v><v>207.34</v><v>Diversified Retail</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587176053123</v><v>27</v><v>204.14</v><v>2214184599200</v><v>AMAZON.COM, INC.</v><v>AMAZON.COM, INC.</v><v>204.96</v><v>28.758299999999998</v><v>200.95</v><v>206.26</v><v>10734920000</v><v>AMZN</v><v>AMAZON.COM, INC. (XNAS:AMZN)</v><v>7720397</v><v>45540688</v><v>1996</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>28</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=bn6lmw&amp;q=XNYS%3aBE&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="3"><v>5</v><v>BLOOM ENERGY CORPORATION (XNYS:BE)</v><v>2</v><v>9</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>bn6lmw</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>180.8999</v><v>15.15</v><v>3.1987999999999999</v><v>9.7750000000000004</v><v>8.1792000000000004E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Bloom Energy Corporation is engaged in stationary fuel cell power generation by market share. The Company provides distributed energy technology solutions to customers. The Company manufactures advanced and versatile fuel cell energy platforms, supporting the commercial availability of two products: the Bloom Energy Server for generating electricity and the Bloom Electrolyzer for producing hydrogen. With approximately 1.4 gigawatts (GW) of Energy Server systems deployed in more than 1,000 locations and nine countries. Its solid oxide fuel cell technology platform is the foundation for its Energy Server system and Bloom Electrolyzer. The Bloom Energy Server system is designed to deliver reliable, resilient, clean and affordable energy for utilities and organizations alike. Its Energy Server system is designed to deliver reliable electricity. The Bloom Electrolyzer is designed to provide hydrogen solutions based on the same solid oxide platform as its Energy Server systems.</v><v>2214</v><v>New York Stock Exchange</v><v>XNYS</v><v>XNYS</v><v>4353 N 1st St, SAN JOSE, CA, 95134-1259 US</v><v>129.94</v><v>Machinery, Equipment &amp; Components</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587132140623</v><v>30</v><v>122</v><v>36270674037</v><v>BLOOM ENERGY CORPORATION</v><v>BLOOM ENERGY CORPORATION</v><v>123.44</v><v>119.51</v><v>129.285</v><v>280548200</v><v>BE</v><v>BLOOM ENERGY CORPORATION (XNYS:BE)</v><v>1895646</v><v>10552084</v><v>2001</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>31</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1rk52&amp;q=XNAS%3aEBAY&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>EBAY INC. (XNAS:EBAY)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1rk52</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>101.15</v><v>58.71</v><v>1.3123</v><v>2.1</v><v>2.3861E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>eBay Inc. is a global commerce company. The Company's technology empowers buyers and sellers in more than 190 markets around the world. The Company's business includes its online marketplace located at www.ebay.com and its localized counterparts, its off-platform marketplaces and its suite of mobile apps. It provides a number of features for its sellers and buyers that align with its approach of leveraging technology, including generative AI, to enhance the marketplace experience for its customers. For sellers, the Company is focused on simplifying their business processes to help drive their sales. The Company offers the eBay International Shipping program for sellers in the United States. For buyers, it is changing the way they find inventory through discovery, personalization and other experiences. It launched Explore, an AI-powered shopping feed enabling users to browse a list of personalized recommendations based on their interests, style preferences, and sizes.</v><v>12300</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>2025 Hamilton Avenue, SAN JOSE, CA, 95125 US</v><v>90.57</v><v>Software &amp; IT Services</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587160207811</v><v>33</v><v>88.94</v><v>40369280000</v><v>EBAY INC.</v><v>EBAY INC.</v><v>89.92</v><v>21.101099999999999</v><v>88.01</v><v>90.11</v><v>448000000</v><v>EBAY</v><v>EBAY INC. (XNAS:EBAY)</v><v>663152</v><v>5129922</v><v>1998</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>34</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=bwv9yc&amp;q=XNAS%3aEVGO&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>EVGO INC. (XNAS:EVGO)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>bwv9yc</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>5.18</v><v>1.64</v><v>2.8105000000000002</v><v>2.5000000000000001E-2</v><v>1.506E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>EVgo Inc. provides electric vehicle charging solutions. The Company owns and operates a public direct current fast charging network for electric vehicles in the United States. Its network of charging stations provides EV charging infrastructure to consumers and businesses. It partners with automotive original equipment manufacturers (OEMs), fleet and rideshare operators, retail hosts such as grocery stores, shopping centers, gas stations, parking lot operators, governments and other organizations and property owners to locate and deploy its EV charging infrastructure. In addition to the provision of EV charging infrastructure, it is developing and deploying software-based, value-added services to drivers and partners.</v><v>376</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>1661 East Franklin Avenue, EL SEGUNDO, CA, 90245 US</v><v>1.7050000000000001</v><v>Electrical Utilities &amp; IPPs</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587085543753</v><v>36</v><v>1.67</v><v>527545697</v><v>EVGO INC.</v><v>EVGO INC.</v><v>1.67</v><v>0</v><v>1.66</v><v>1.6850000000000001</v><v>313083500</v><v>EVGO</v><v>EVGO INC. (XNAS:EVGO)</v><v>441052</v><v>5226383</v><v>2020</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>37</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1tym7&amp;q=XNYS%3aGLW&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>CORNING INCORPORATED (XNYS:GLW)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1tym7</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>162.09989999999999</v><v>37.31</v><v>1.0811999999999999</v><v>4.53</v><v>3.5238999999999999E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Corning Incorporated operates as an innovator in materials science. Its segments include Optical Communications, Display Technologies, Specialty Materials, Environmental Technologies, and Life Sciences. Its Optical Communications segment manufactures carrier network and enterprise network components for the telecommunications industry. Its Display Technologies segment manufactures glass substrates for flat-panel displays, including liquid crystal displays and organic light-emitting diodes. Its Specialty Materials segment manufactures products that provide material formulations for glass, glass ceramics and fluoride crystals for customer needs. Its Environmental Technologies segment manufactures ceramic substrates and filters for emission control systems in mobile applications. Its Life Sciences segment develops, manufactures and supplies laboratory products, including labware, equipment, media, serum and reagents, enabling workflow solutions for drug discovery and bioproduction.</v><v>67200</v><v>New York Stock Exchange</v><v>XNYS</v><v>XNYS</v><v>One Riverfront Plaza, CORNING, NY, 14831 US</v><v>133.46</v><v>Electronic Equipment &amp; Parts</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587147337501</v><v>39</v><v>130.14009999999999</v><v>114317689584</v><v>CORNING INCORPORATED</v><v>CORNING INCORPORATED</v><v>132.29</v><v>72.456000000000003</v><v>128.55000000000001</v><v>133.08000000000001</v><v>859014800</v><v>GLW</v><v>CORNING INCORPORATED (XNYS:GLW)</v><v>1709174</v><v>14065884</v><v>1936</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>40</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1u3rw&amp;q=XNAS%3aGOOGL&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>ALPHABET INC. (XNAS:GOOGL)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1u3rw</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>349</v><v>140.53</v><v>1.1462000000000001</v><v>6.77</v><v>2.4752999999999997E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Alphabet Inc. is a holding company. The Company's segments include Google Services, Google Cloud, and Other Bets. The Google Services segment includes products and services such as ads, Android, Chrome, devices, Google Maps, Google Play, Search, and YouTube. The Google Cloud segment includes infrastructure and platform services, collaboration tools, and other services for enterprise customers. Its Other Bets segment is engaged in the sale of healthcare-related services and Internet services. Its Google Cloud provides enterprise-ready cloud services, including Google Cloud Platform and Google Workspace. Google Cloud Platform provides access to solutions such as artificial intelligence (AI) offerings, including its AI infrastructure, Vertex AI platform, and Gemini for Google Cloud; cybersecurity, and data and analytics. Google Workspace includes cloud-based communication and collaboration tools for enterprises, such as Calendar, Gmail, Docs, Drive, and Meet.</v><v>190820</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA, 94043 US</v><v>280.53500000000003</v><v>Software &amp; IT Services</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587168321093</v><v>42</v><v>277.08999999999997</v><v>3390426190000</v><v>ALPHABET INC.</v><v>ALPHABET INC.</v><v>278.39999999999998</v><v>25.9269</v><v>273.5</v><v>280.27</v><v>12097000000</v><v>GOOGL</v><v>ALPHABET INC. (XNAS:GOOGL)</v><v>5244974</v><v>30551666</v><v>2015</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>43</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=afu527&amp;q=XETR%3aTPE&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>PVA TePla AG (XETR:TPE)</v><v>2</v><v>10</v><v>Finance</v><v>11</v><v>en-US</v><v>afu527</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>33.479999999999997</v><v>11.05</v><v>1.3596999999999999</v><v>0.06</v><v>2.0040000000000001E-3</v><v>EUR</v><v>PVA TePla AG is a Germany-based company that provides vacuum solutions for high temperature and plasma treatment processes, as well as plant engineering solutions. The Company operates through two segments: Industrial Systems and Semiconductor Systems. The Industrials Systems segment specializes in the development, construction and marketing of vacuum heat treatment furnaces for processing materials at high temperatures. The Semiconductor Systems segment provides systems for the semiconductor and solar industry ranging from systems for the production of silicon crystals for the semiconductor, solar and opto-electronic industry to systems for plasma treatment in the semiconductor assembly, as well as systems for non-destructive, ultrasonic quality inspection of materials. The Company operates through subsidiaries in Europe, Asia and North America.</v><v>944</v><v>Xetra</v><v>XETR</v><v>XETR</v><v>Im Westpark 10-12, WETTENBERG, HESSEN, 35435 DE</v><v>30.14</v><v>Semiconductors &amp; Semiconductor Equipment</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.576481481483</v><v>45</v><v>29</v><v>585074700</v><v>PVA TePla AG</v><v>PVA TePla AG</v><v>30</v><v>41.4651</v><v>29.94</v><v>30</v><v>21749990</v><v>TPE</v><v>PVA TePla AG (XETR:TPE)</v><v>27502</v><v>133530</v><v>2008</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>46</v></rv><rv s="4"><v>12</v><v>Lithium Americas Corp (XNYS:LAC)</v><v>13</v><v>14</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>cazeww</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>10.52</v><v>2.31</v><v>0.13500000000000001</v><v>3.5619999999999999E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Lithium Americas Corp. is a Canada-based lithium company. The Company focused on developing, building, and operating lithium deposits and chemical processing facilities. The Company’s flagship asset is Thacker Pass, a sedimentary-based lithium deposit located in the McDermitt Caldera in Humboldt County, in northern Nevada. The Company is focused on developing the 100%-owned Thacker Pass lithium project in northern Nevada, the United States of America. Thacker Pass is approximately 100 kilometers (km) north-northwest of Winnemucca, Nevada, approximately 33 km west-northwest of Orovada, Nevada, and 33 km due south of the Oregon border. The Thacker Pass area encompasses approximately 7,900 hectares (ha) and lies within and is surrounded by public lands. The Company's subsidiaries are LAC Management LLC, Lithium Nevada Ventures LLC, KV Project LLC and others.</v><v>87</v><v>New York Stock Exchange</v><v>XNYS</v><v>XNYS</v><v>3260 - 666 Burrard St, VANCOUVER, BC, V6C 2X8 CA</v><v>3.93</v><v>Metals &amp; Mining</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587077881253</v><v>3.83</v><v>1363341685</v><v>Lithium Americas Corp</v><v>Lithium Americas Corp</v><v>3.88</v><v>3.79</v><v>3.9249999999999998</v><v>347348200</v><v>LAC</v><v>Lithium Americas Corp (XNYS:LAC)</v><v>719019</v><v>8401985</v><v>2023</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>48</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=ayqwc7&amp;q=XNYS%3aLAC&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="3"><v>5</v><v>Lithium Argentina AG (XNYS:LAR)</v><v>2</v><v>9</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>ayqwc7</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>8.8000000000000007</v><v>1.71</v><v>1.3309</v><v>0.05</v><v>7.541E-3</v><v>USD</v><v>Lithium Argentina AG is a Switzerland based company, operating in the mining industry. The Company is a resource and materials company focused on lithium production, which involves pumping the lithium into ponds allowing for the water to evaporate and the mineral fall out of suspension. Lithium is a material used primarily in lithium-ion batteries, which have applications in personal electronic devices electric cars among other products. The Company has stakes in multiple lithium-ion production facilities located primarily in Argentina such as the Cauchari-Olaroz lithium brine operation, the Cauchari-Olaroz Project, which is located in Jujuy, Argentina, the Pastos Grandes project, located in Salta Province, and the Sal de la Puna Project.</v><v>850</v><v>New York Stock Exchange</v><v>XNYS</v><v>XNYS</v><v>Dammstrasse 19, ZUG, ZUG, 6300 CH</v><v>6.68</v><v>Metals &amp; Mining</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587126296094</v><v>50</v><v>6.4249999999999998</v><v>1094402436</v><v>Lithium Argentina AG</v><v>Lithium Argentina AG</v><v>6.59</v><v>6.63</v><v>6.68</v><v>163832700</v><v>LAR</v><v>Lithium Argentina AG (XNYS:LAR)</v><v>652081</v><v>3434712</v><v>2025</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>51</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1wuoc&amp;q=XNYS%3aLEU&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>CENTRUS ENERGY CORP. (XNYS:LEU)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1wuoc</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>464.25</v><v>49.400100000000002</v><v>1.3818999999999999</v><v>5.23</v><v>3.1035E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Centrus Energy Corp. is a supplier of nuclear fuel components for the nuclear power industry. Its segments include Low-Enriched Uranium (LEU) and Technical Solutions. Its LEU segment supplies various components of nuclear fuel to commercial customers from its global network of suppliers. The LEU segment consists of two components: SWU and natural uranium hexafluoride. It supplies LEU and its components to both domestic and international utilities for use in nuclear reactors worldwide. It provides LEU from multiple sources, including its inventory, medium- and long-term supply contracts, and spot purchases. It also sells natural uranium hexafluoride and occasionally sells uranium concentrates. The Technical Solutions segment provides advanced engineering, design, and manufacturing services to government and private sector customers. It is deploying uranium enrichment and other capabilities necessary to produce advanced nuclear fuel to power existing reactors around the world.</v><v>300</v><v>New York Stock Exchange</v><v>XNYS</v><v>XNYS</v><v>6901 Rockledge Dr, Suite 800, BETHESDA, MD, 20817 US</v><v>175.7824</v><v>Uranium</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587120289063</v><v>53</v><v>167.08</v><v>3416717300</v><v>CENTRUS ENERGY CORP.</v><v>CENTRUS ENERGY CORP.</v><v>170</v><v>41.771799999999999</v><v>168.52</v><v>173.75</v><v>19664560</v><v>LEU</v><v>CENTRUS ENERGY CORP. (XNYS:LEU)</v><v>168990</v><v>740463</v><v>1998</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>54</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1slm7&amp;q=XNAS%3aMETA&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>META PLATFORMS, INC. (XNAS:META)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1slm7</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>796.25</v><v>479.8</v><v>1.3371</v><v>21.065000000000001</v><v>3.9272999999999995E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Meta Platforms, Inc. is building human connections, powered by artificial intelligence and immersive technologies. The Company's products enable people to connect and share with friends and family through mobile devices, personal computers, virtual reality (VR) and mixed reality (MR) headsets, augmented reality (AR), and wearables. It also helps people discover and learn about what is going on in the world around them, enabling people to share their experiences, ideas, photos, videos, and other content with audiences ranging from their closest family members and friends to the public at large. The Company's segments include Family of Apps (FoA) and Reality Labs (RL). FoA segment includes Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, WhatsApp and Threads. RL segment includes its virtual, augmented, and mixed reality related consumer hardware, software and content. Its product offerings in VR include its Meta Quest devices, as well as software and content available through the Meta Horizon Store.</v><v>78865</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>1 Meta Way, MENLO PARK, CA, 94025 US</v><v>559.05999999999995</v><v>Software &amp; IT Services</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587174385939</v><v>56</v><v>546.77</v><v>1410087786975</v><v>META PLATFORMS, INC.</v><v>META PLATFORMS, INC.</v><v>550</v><v>19.070599999999999</v><v>536.38</v><v>557.44500000000005</v><v>2529555000</v><v>META</v><v>META PLATFORMS, INC. (XNAS:META)</v><v>4956958</v><v>14697705</v><v>2004</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>57</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Public_domain</v><v>Public domain</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microsoft</v><v>Wikipedia</v></rv><rv s="5"><v>59</v><v>60</v></rv><rv s="6"><v>19</v><v>https://www.bing.com/th?id=AMMS_e6e837c7bf3a77408619758b7447855a&amp;qlt=95</v><v>61</v><v>0</v><v>https://www.bing.com/images/search?form=xlimg&amp;q=microsoft</v><v>Image of MICROSOFT CORPORATION</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1xzim&amp;q=XNAS%3aMSFT&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="7"><v>15</v><v>MICROSOFT CORPORATION (XNAS:MSFT)</v><v>17</v><v>18</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1xzim</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>555.45000000000005</v><v>344.79</v><v>1.1069</v><v>7.8849999999999998</v><v>2.1965999999999999E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Microsoft Corporation is a technology company. The Company develops and supports software, services, devices, and solutions. The Company’s segments include Productivity and Business Processes, Intelligent Cloud, and More Personal Computing. The Productivity and Business Processes segment consists of products and services in its portfolio of productivity, communication, and information services. This segment primarily comprises: Office Commercial, Office Consumer, LinkedIn, and Dynamics business solutions. The Intelligent Cloud segment consists of server products and cloud services, including Azure and other cloud services, SQL Server, Windows Server, Visual Studio, System Center, and related Client Access Licenses (CALs), and Nuance and GitHub; and Enterprise Services, including enterprise support services, industry solutions and Nuance professional services. The More Personal Computing segment primarily comprises Windows, Devices, Gaming, and search and news advertising.</v><v>228000</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>One Microsoft Way, REDMOND, WA, 98052 US</v><v>368.15</v><v>62</v><v>Software &amp; IT Services</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587166503909</v><v>63</v><v>364.375</v><v>2724054870505</v><v>MICROSOFT CORPORATION</v><v>MICROSOFT CORPORATION</v><v>364.95</v><v>22.953099999999999</v><v>358.96</v><v>366.84500000000003</v><v>7425629000</v><v>MSFT</v><v>MICROSOFT CORPORATION (XNAS:MSFT)</v><v>5331322</v><v>34533079</v><v>1993</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>64</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1ye2w&amp;q=XNYS%3aNEE&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>NEXTERA ENERGY, INC. (XNYS:NEE)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1ye2w</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>95.91</v><v>61.72</v><v>0.71860000000000002</v><v>0.28000000000000003</v><v>3.0420000000000004E-3</v><v>USD</v><v>NextEra Energy, Inc. is an electric power and energy infrastructure company. It operates through its wholly owned subsidiaries, NextEra Energy Resources, LLC and NextEra Energy Transmission, LLC (collectively, NEER) and Florida Power &amp; Light Company (FPL). Its segments include NEER and FPL. FPL segment is a rate-regulated electric utility engaged in the generation, transmission, distribution and sale of electric energy in Florida. FPL has approximately 35,052 megawatts of net generating capacity, over 91,000 circuit miles of transmission and distribution lines and 921 substations. The NEER segment owns, develops, constructs, manages and operates electric generation facilities in wholesale energy markets in the United States and Canada and includes assets and investments in other businesses with a clean energy focus, such as battery storage, natural gas pipelines, and renewable fuels. It owns, develops, constructs and operates rate-regulated transmission facilities in North America.</v><v>17400</v><v>New York Stock Exchange</v><v>XNYS</v><v>XNYS</v><v>700 Universe Blvd, JUNO BEACH, FL, 33408 US</v><v>92.7</v><v>Electrical Utilities &amp; IPPs</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587155428126</v><v>66</v><v>91.65</v><v>192371586260</v><v>NEXTERA ENERGY, INC.</v><v>NEXTERA ENERGY, INC.</v><v>92.28</v><v>27.970300000000002</v><v>92.05</v><v>92.33</v><v>2083522000</v><v>NEE</v><v>NEXTERA ENERGY, INC. (XNYS:NEE)</v><v>1055475</v><v>10650922</v><v>1984</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>67</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1yv52&amp;q=XNAS%3aNVDA&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>NVIDIA CORPORATION (XNAS:NVDA)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1yv52</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>212.18989999999999</v><v>86.62</v><v>2.3109000000000002</v><v>4.63</v><v>2.8031999999999998E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>NVIDIA Corporation is an artificial intelligence (AI) infrastructure company. The Company is engaged in accelerated computing to help solve the challenging computational problems. Its segments include Compute &amp; Networking and Graphics. The Compute &amp; Networking segment includes its Data Center accelerated computing and networking platforms and AI solutions and software, and automotive platforms and autonomous and electric vehicle solutions, including software. The Graphics segment includes GeForce GPUs for gaming and personal computers (PCs), and Quadro/NVIDIA RTX GPUs for enterprise workstation graphics. Its technology stack includes the foundational NVIDIA CUDA development platform that runs on all NVIDIA GPUs, as well as hundreds of domain-specific software libraries, frameworks, algorithms, software development kits (SDKs), and application programming interfaces (APIs). Its platforms address four markets, which include Data Center, Gaming, Professional Visualization, and Automotive.</v><v>42000</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>2788 San Tomas Expressway, SANTA CLARA, CA, 95051 US</v><v>170.16</v><v>Semiconductors &amp; Semiconductor Equipment</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.58714688594</v><v>69</v><v>166.96</v><v>4126140000000</v><v>NVIDIA CORPORATION</v><v>NVIDIA CORPORATION</v><v>167</v><v>34.640300000000003</v><v>165.17</v><v>169.8</v><v>24300000000</v><v>NVDA</v><v>NVIDIA CORPORATION (XNAS:NVDA)</v><v>31102041</v><v>195966990</v><v>1998</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>70</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=bvsk7w&amp;q=XNYS%3aPLTR&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>PALANTIR TECHNOLOGIES INC. (XNAS:PLTR)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>bvsk7w</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>207.52</v><v>66.12</v><v>1.661</v><v>3.08</v><v>2.2391999999999999E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Palantir Technologies Inc. is engaged in building software to assist in counterterrorism investigations and operations. The Company has built four principal software platforms, including Palantir Gotham (Gotham), Palantir Foundry (Foundry), Palantir Apollo (Apollo), and Palantir Artificial Intelligence Platform (AIP). Apollo is a cloud-agnostic, single control layer that coordinates ongoing delivery of new features, security updates, and platform configurations, helping to ensure the continuous operation of critical systems. Gotham enables users to identify patterns hidden deep within datasets, ranging from signals intelligence sources to reports from confidential informants. Foundry transforms the ways organizations operate by creating a central operating system for their data. AIP enables responsible artificial intelligence (AI)-advantage across the enterprise by using primary, core components built to effectively activate large language models and other AI within any organization.</v><v>4429</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>1200 17Th Street, Floor 15, DENVER, CO, 80202 US</v><v>141.26</v><v>Software &amp; IT Services</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587132441404</v><v>72</v><v>138.97999999999999</v><v>336200062730</v><v>PALANTIR TECHNOLOGIES INC.</v><v>PALANTIR TECHNOLOGIES INC.</v><v>140.08000000000001</v><v>222.2345</v><v>137.55000000000001</v><v>140.63</v><v>2390671000</v><v>PLTR</v><v>PALANTIR TECHNOLOGIES INC. (XNAS:PLTR)</v><v>6127425</v><v>48558034</v><v>2003</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>73</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a1zyw7&amp;q=XNAS%3aPLUG&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>PLUG POWER INC. (XNAS:PLUG)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a1zyw7</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>4.58</v><v>0.69</v><v>1.7173</v><v>2.5000000000000001E-2</v><v>1.1682E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Plug Power Inc. is engaged in offering end-to-end green hydrogen ecosystem, from production, storage, and delivery to energy generation, to help its customers meet their business goals. The Company develops commercially viable hydrogen and fuel cell product solutions. It provides electrolyzers that allow customers, such as refineries, producers of chemicals, steel, fertilizer and commercial refueling stations, to generate hydrogen on-site. It focuses on industrial mobility applications, including electric forklifts and electric industrial vehicles, at multi-shift high volume manufacturing and high throughput distribution sites and environmental benefits; stationary power systems that supports critical operations, such as data centers, microgrids and generation facilities, in either a backup power or continuous power role and replace batteries, diesel generators or the grid for telecommunication logistics, transportation, and utility customers; and production of hydrogen.</v><v>2582</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>125 Vista Boulevard, SLINGERLANDS, NY, 12159 US</v><v>2.2000000000000002</v><v>Renewable Energy</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587144478908</v><v>75</v><v>2.16</v><v>3017912575</v><v>PLUG POWER INC.</v><v>PLUG POWER INC.</v><v>2.17</v><v>0</v><v>2.14</v><v>2.165</v><v>1393955000</v><v>PLUG</v><v>PLUG POWER INC. (XNAS:PLUG)</v><v>6002836</v><v>84836694</v><v>1999</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>76</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=a24kar&amp;q=XNAS%3aTSLA&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>TESLA, INC. (XNAS:TSLA)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>a24kar</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>498.83</v><v>214.25</v><v>1.9041999999999999</v><v>7.7</v><v>2.1673000000000001E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Tesla, Inc. designs, develops, manufactures, sells and leases high-performance fully electric vehicles and energy generation and storage systems, and offers services related to its products. Its segments include automotive, and energy generation and storage. The automotive segment includes the design, development, manufacturing, sales and leasing of high-performance fully electric vehicles, and sales of automotive regulatory credits. It also includes sales of used vehicles, non-warranty maintenance services and collisions, part sales, paid supercharging, insurance services revenue and retail merchandise sales. The energy generation and storage segment include the design, manufacture, installation, sales and leasing of solar energy generation and energy storage products and related services and sales of solar energy systems incentives. Its consumer vehicles include the Model 3, Y, S, X and Cybertruck. Its lithium-ion battery energy storage products include Powerwall and Megapack.</v><v>134785</v><v>Nasdaq Stock Market</v><v>XNAS</v><v>XNAS</v><v>1 Tesla Road, AUSTIN, TX, 78725 US</v><v>365.41989999999998</v><v>Automobiles &amp; Auto Parts</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587133390625</v><v>78</v><v>361.24</v><v>1362057767360</v><v>TESLA, INC.</v><v>TESLA, INC.</v><v>361.5</v><v>337.53019999999998</v><v>355.28</v><v>362.98</v><v>3752432000</v><v>TSLA</v><v>TESLA, INC. (XNAS:TSLA)</v><v>11600313</v><v>60440754</v><v>2024</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>79</v></rv><rv s="0"><v>https://www.bing.com/financeapi/forcetrigger?t=b19hc7&amp;q=XNYS%3aVRT&amp;form=skydnc</v><v>Learn more on Bing</v></rv><rv s="1"><v>0</v><v>VERTIV HOLDINGS CO (XNYS:VRT)</v><v>2</v><v>7</v><v>Finance</v><v>8</v><v>en-US</v><v>b19hc7</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>282.05</v><v>53.6</v><v>2.0442999999999998</v><v>9.2461000000000002</v><v>3.9475999999999997E-2</v><v>USD</v><v>Vertiv Holdings Co. provides mission-critical digital infrastructure technologies and lifecycle services primarily for data centers, communication networks, and commercial and industrial environments. The Company operates in three business segments: the Americas; Asia Pacific, and Europe, Middle East &amp; Africa. The Company's offerings include alternate current (AC) and direct current (DC) power management, thermal management, low/medium voltage switchgear, busbar, air cooled and liquid cooled thermal management products, integrated modular solutions, racks, single phase UPS, rack power distribution, rack thermal systems, configurable integrated solutions, energy storage solutions, hardware, software for managing IT equipment, management systems for monitoring and controlling digital infrastructure, and services. It also provides preventative maintenance, acceptance testing, engineering and consulting, remote monitoring, training, spare parts, specialized fluid management, and others.</v><v>34000</v><v>New York Stock Exchange</v><v>XNYS</v><v>XNYS</v><v>505 N. Cleveland Ave., WESTERVILLE, OH, 43082 US</v><v>244.99</v><v>Machinery, Equipment &amp; Components</v><v>Stock</v><v>46112.587139062503</v><v>81</v><v>233.25</v><v>93149740314</v><v>VERTIV HOLDINGS CO</v><v>VERTIV HOLDINGS CO</v><v>233.68</v><v>71.399799999999999</v><v>234.22</v><v>243.46610000000001</v><v>382598400</v><v>VRT</v><v>VERTIV HOLDINGS CO (XNYS:VRT)</v><v>1311591</v><v>10648749</v><v>2016</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>82</v></rv><rv s="8"><v>20</v><v>USD/TWD</v><v>21</v><v>22</v><v>Finance</v><v>23</v><v>en-US</v><v>avytar</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>33.295000000000002</v><v>28.734000000000002</v><v>-4.5999999999999999E-2</v><v>-1.436E-3</v><v>TWD</v><v>USD</v><v>32.185000000000002</v><v>Currency Pair</v><v>46112.581111111111</v><v>32.024999999999999</v><v>US Dollar/Taiwan Dollar FX Spot Rate</v><v>32.040999999999997</v><v>32.040999999999997</v><v>31.995000000000001</v><v>USDTWD</v><v>USD/TWD</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>84</v></rv><rv s="8"><v>20</v><v>JPY/TWD</v><v>21</v><v>22</v><v>Finance</v><v>23</v><v>en-US</v><v>ave7kr</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>0.2321</v><v>0.19670000000000001</v><v>4.0000000000000002E-4</v><v>1.9940000000000001E-3</v><v>TWD</v><v>JPY</v><v>0.20180000000000001</v><v>Currency Pair</v><v>46112.587152777778</v><v>0.2006</v><v>Japanese Yen/Taiwan Dollar FX Cross Rate</v><v>0.2006</v><v>0.2006</v><v>0.20100000000000001</v><v>JPYTWD</v><v>JPY/TWD</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>86</v></rv><rv s="8"><v>20</v><v>USD/JPY</v><v>21</v><v>24</v><v>Finance</v><v>23</v><v>en-US</v><v>avyomw</v><v>268435456</v><v>1</v><v>Powered by Refinitiv</v><v>160.46</v><v>139.86000000000001</v><v>-0.53</v><v>-3.3179999999999998E-3</v><v>JPY</v><v>USD</v><v>159.97</v><v>Currency Pair</v><v>46112.587118055555</v><v>159.08000000000001</v><v>US Dollar/Japanese Yen FX Spot Rate</v><v>159.72999999999999</v><v>159.72</v><v>159.19</v><v>USDJPY</v><v>USD/JPY</v></rv><rv s="2"><v>88</v></rv></rvData>